A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5 FA440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaigns, 1956-1970; 5; 98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
  - 1968 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 8
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Minnesota, 1968 May 8 (Box 95, Folder 1300)
    - Poll - Trust and Confidence and Mental Image: A National Image, 1968 July 3 (Box 95, Folder 1301)
    - Poll - Attitude Toward Presidential Candidates, 1968 May (Box 95, Folder 1302)
    - Poll - Northwestern University, 1968 July (Box 95, Folder 1303)
    - Polls - Summaries of Recent Major Polls, 1968 August (Box 95, Folder 1304)
    - Hinman Poll Book, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1305)
    - Aldrich, Richard, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1306)
    - Alfange, Dean, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1307)
    - American Heritage Foundation, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1308)
    - American Nationalities for Rockefeller, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1309)
    - Auxiliary Groups, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1310)
    - Block, Peter, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1311)
    - Business and Professional, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1312)
    - Citizens Activities, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1313)
    - Council of Republican Organizations, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1314)
    - Correspondence Unit, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1315)
    - Diamond, Henry, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1316)
    - Ethnic Groups, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1317)
    - Governor's Christmas Card List, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1318)
    - Hanswan, Samuel, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1319)
    - Jackovies, J.R., 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1320)
    - Job Seekers, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1321)
    - Lionel Hampton, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1322)
    - Messages, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1323)
    - Mott, Stewart - Coalition for Republican Alternative, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1324)
    - National Bipartisan Movement, Inc., 1968 (Box 95, Folder 1325-1326)
    - National Bipartisan Movement, Inc., 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1327)
    - New York Republican State Committees, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1328)
    - Nationalities, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1329)
    - Organization Charts, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1330)
    - Polish American Committee, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1331)
    - Position Papers - NAR - Domestic, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1332)
    - Press Releases, 1968 June 20-July 24 (Box 96, Folder 1333)
    - New York State Republican Delegates List, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1334)
    - Stanley Ross, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1335)
    - Ritterspovn, B.A., Jr., 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1336)
    - Scandanavians, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1337)
    - Schafer, George, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1338)
    - Slovaks for Rockefeller, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1339)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Idaho, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1340)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Illinois, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1341)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Indiana, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 1342)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Iowa, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1343)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Kansas, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1344)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Kentucky, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1345)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Lousiana, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1346)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Maine, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1347)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Maryland, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1348)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1349)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Michigan, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1350)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Minnesota, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1351)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Mississippi, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1352)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Missouri, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1353)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Montana, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1354)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Nebraska, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1355)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Nevada, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1356)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - New Hampshire, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1357)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - New Jersey, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1358)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - New Mexico, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 1359)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - New York, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1360)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - North Carolina, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1361)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - North Dakota, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1362)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Ohio, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1363)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1364)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Oregon, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1365)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1366)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Rhode Island, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1367)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - South Carolina, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1368)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - South Dakota, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1369)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Tennessee, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1370)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Texas, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1371)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Utah, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1372)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Vermont, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1373)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Virginia, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1374)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Washington, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1375)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - West Virginia, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1376)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1377)
    - Colleges - "New Majority" - Wyoming, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1378)
    - Campaign Press Releases, 1968 March-August (Box 99, Folder 1379-1382)
    - State Committee Chair Appointments - Press Releases, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1383)
    - Republican National Convention - Press Releases, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1384)
    - Negro Vote, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1385)
    - Personnel, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1386)
    - Rockefeller Plea to Public, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1387)
    - Press Clipping Service, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1388)
    - Press Coverage, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1389)
    - Questions - NAR answers to questions, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1390)
    - Rafferty, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1391)
    - Reagan Candidacy, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1392)
    - Record, The - "Survey shows Swing to Rocky", 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1393)
    - Rockefeller Record, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1394)
    - Rockefeller Strategy, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1395)
    - Spivack Report, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1395A)
    - Speeches, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1395B)
    - Scientists and Engineers Poll, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1396)
    - Secret Service Assigned to NAR, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1397)
    - Shafer, Raymond, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1398)
    - South Dakota, NAR Speech, 1968 June 27 (Box 99, Folder 1399)
    - Student Poll, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1400)
    - Telegrams, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1401)
    - Tickler File, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1402)
    - Time, Inc. Luncheon, 1968 June 17 (Box 100, Folder 1403)
    - TV Debates - Equal Time, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1404)
    - U.S. News and World Report - Interview, 1968 June 24 (Box 100, Folder 1405)
    - University of Denver - News Conference, 1958 May 28 (Box 100, Folder 1406)
    - Vietnam - News Clippings, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1407)
    - New York Times, James Reston, "The Final Irony of Death", 1968 June 9 (Box 100, Folder 1408)
    - Weekly Newspaper Advertising, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1409)
    - Rockefeller to "Win", 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1410)
    - NAR Speeches, biography, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1411)
    - Delegate Information (Maryland), 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1412)
    - Staff Memoranda, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1413)
    - Organization Chart, Committees, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1414)
    - Secret Service Teams, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1415)
    - Advanceman, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1416, 1418, 1419, 1421)
    - Moore, Tom - Speakers Bureau, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 1417)
    - NAR Tentative Schedule, 1968 June 5-15 (Box 100, Folder 1420)
    - Advanceman Procedure, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1422)
    - Telephone Numbers, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1423)
    - Airline Manifests, 1968 May-July (Box 101, Folder 1424)
    - Telegrams, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1425)
    - Republican Volunteers, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1426)
    - Polls, 1968 February-May (Box 101, Folder 1427)
    - Miscellaneous, Political Calendar of various candidates, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1428)
    - Arts and Entertainment - Schedules, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1429)
    - State Delegate Book - Table of Contents, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1430)
    - State Delegate Book - Alabama, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1431)
    - State Delegate Book - Alaska, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1432)
    - State Delegate Book - Arizona, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1433)
    - State Delegate Book - Arkansas, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1434)
    - State Delegate Book - California, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1435)
    - State Delegate Book - Colorado, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1436)
    - State Delegate Book - Connecticut, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1437)
    - State Delegate Book - Delaware, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1438)
    - State Delegate Book - Florida, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1439)
    - State Delegate Book - Georgia, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1440)
    - State Delegate Book - Hawaii, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1441)
    - State Delegate Book - District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1442)
    - State Delegate Book - Idaho, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1443)
    - State Delegate Book - Illinois, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 1444)
    - State Delegate Book - Indiana, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1445)
    - State Delegate Book - Iowa, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1446)
    - State Delegate Book - Kansas, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1447)
    - State Delegate Book - Kentucky, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1448)
    - State Delegate Book - Louisiana, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1449)
    - State Delegate Book - Maine, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1450)
    - State Delegate Book - Maryland, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1451)
    - State Delegate Book - Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1452)
    - State Delegate Book - Michigan, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 1453)
    - State Delegate Book - Minnesota, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1454)
    - State Delegate Book - Missouri, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1455)
    - State Delegate Book - Mississippi, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1456)
    - State Delegate Book - New York, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1457)
    - State Delegate Book - Montana, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1458)
    - State Delegate Book - Nebraska, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1459)
    - State Delegate Book - Nevada, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1460)
    - State Delegate Book - New Hampshire, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1461)
    - State Delegate Book - New Jersey, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1462)
    - State Delegate Book - New Mexico, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1463)
    - State Delegate Book - North Carolina, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1464)
    - State Delegate Book - North Dakota, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1464)
    - State Delegate Book - Ohio, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1465)
    - State Delegate Book - Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1466)
    - State Delegate Book - Oregon, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1467)
    - State Delegate Book - Rhode Island, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1468)
    - State Delegate Book - Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1469)
    - State Delegate Book - Puerto Rico, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1470)
    - State Delegate Book - South Carolina, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1471)
    - State Delegate Book - South Dakota, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1472)
    - State Delegate Book - Tennessee, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1473)
    - State Delegate Book - Texas, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1474)
    - State Delegate Book - Utah, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1475)
    - State Delegate Book - Vermont, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1476)
    - State Delegate Book - Virgin Island, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1477)
    - State Delegate Book - Virginia, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1478)
    - State Delegate Book - Washington, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1479)
    - State Delegate Book - West Virginia, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1480)
    - State Delegate Book - Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1481)
    - State Delegate Book - Wyoming, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1482)
    - Republican National Convention Book, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1483)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Alabama, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1484-1485)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Alaska, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1486-1487)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Arizona, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1488-1489)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Arkansas, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1490-1491)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - California, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 1492-1495)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - California, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 1496-1502)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Colorado, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 1503)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Colorado, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 1504)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Connecticut, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 1505-1507)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Delaware, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 1508-1510)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 1511)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 1512-1513)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Florida, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 1514-1518)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Georgia, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 1519-1523)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Hawaii, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 1524)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Hawaii, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 1525)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Idaho, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 1526-1527)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Illinois, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 1528-1531)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Indiana, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 1532-1533)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Iowa, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 1534-1537)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Kansas, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 1538-1539)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Kentucky, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 1540-1541)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Louisiana, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 1542-1543)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Maine, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 1544-1545)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Maryland, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 1546-1547)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 116, Folder 1548-1551)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Michigan, 1968 (Box 116, Folder 1552-1553)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Michigan, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 1554-1555)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Minnesota, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 1556-1558)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Mississippi, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 1559-1560)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Missouri, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 1561-1563)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Montana, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 1564-1565)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Nebraska, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 1566-1567)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Nevada, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 1568-1569)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - New Hampshire, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 1570-1571)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - New Jersey, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 1572-1573)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - New Mexico, 1968 (Box 119, Folder 1574-1575)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - New York, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 1576)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - North Carolina, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 1577-1578)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - North Dakota, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 1579-1580)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Ohio, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 1581-1584)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 1585)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1586)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Oregon, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1587-1589)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1590-1593)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 1594-1595)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Puerto Rico, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 1596)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Rhode Island, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 1597-1598)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - South Carolina, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 1599-1602)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Tennessee, 1968 (Box 124, Folder 1603-1604)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Texas, 1968 (Box 124, Folder 1605-1607)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Utah, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 1608-1609)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Vermont, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 1610-1611)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Virginia, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 1612-1613)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Virgin Islands, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 1614-1615)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Washington, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1616-1617)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - West Virginia, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1618-1620)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 1621-1622)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1623-1624)
    - Republican National Convention Delegates - Wyoming, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1625-1626)
    - Republican National Convention - Lists, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1627)
    - Republican National Convention - NAR "Opposition", 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1628)
    - Republican National Convention - NAR - Reagan as Vice President, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1629)
    - Republican National Convention - Campaign Organization, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1630)
    - Republican National Convention - "New Majority for Rockefeller", 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1631)
    - Republican National Convention - Candidacy Announcement, 1968 April 30 (Box 127, Folder 1632)
    - Republican National Convention - Groups for NAR, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1633)
    - Republican National Convention - Strategy Analysis, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1634)
    - Republican National Convention - 1964 staff, press releases, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 1635)
    - Presidential Campaign - Mailings, Press Releases, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 1636)
    - Presidential Campaign - Ronald Reagan, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 1637-1639)
    - Presidential Campaign - Richard Nixon, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 1640)
    - Campaign Correspondence - AA - ALD, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 1641-1647)
    - Campaign Correspondence - ALE - ANDERSON A-E, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 1648-1653)
    - Campaign Correspondence - ANDERSON F-K - ARNZ, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 1654-1661)
    - Campaign Correspondence - ASA - BAIRD, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 1662-1667)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BAK - BARR, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 1668-1678)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BARS - BEF, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 1679-1687)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BEG - BERN, 1968 (Box 134, Folder 1688-1695)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BERR - BLACK, 1968 (Box 135, Folder 1696-1704)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BLACKA - BORM, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 1705-1714)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BORN - BRAN, 1968 (Box 137, Folder 1715-1722)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BRAS - BROOK A-Z, 1968 (Box 138, Folder 1723-1730)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BROOL - BUG, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 1731-1741)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BUH - BUT, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 1742-1750)
    - Campaign Correspondence - BUY - CAQ, 1968 (Box 141, Folder 1751-1760)
    - Campaign Correspondence - CAR - CAT, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 1761-1770)
    - Campaign Correspondence - CAU - CHR, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 1771-1782)
    - Campaign Correspondence - CHU - COHEN, 1968 (Box 144, Folder 1783-1796)
    - Campaign Correspondence - COHI - COOPER A-G, 1968 (Box 145, Folder 1797-1811)
    - Campaign Correspondence - COOPER H-Z - CRANZ, 1968 (Box 146, Folder 1812-1823)
    - Campaign Correpondence - CRAS - DALS, 1968 (Box 147, Folder 1824-1836)
    - Campaign Correpondence - DALT - DAX, 1968 (Box 148, Folder 1837-1846)
    - Campaign Correpondence - DAY - DER, 1968 (Box 149, Folder 1847-1856)
    - Campaign Correpondence - DESA - DOH, 1968 (Box 150, Folder 1857-1868)
    - Campaign Correpondence - DOL - DUM, 1968 (Box 151, Folder 1869-1881)
    - Campaign Correpondence - DUNA - EH, 1968 (Box 152, Folder 1882-1891)
    - Campaign Correpondence - EIA - ERI, 1968 (Box 153, Folder 1892-1901)
    - Campaign Correpondence - ERL - FEH, 1968 (Box 154, Folder 1902-1916)
    - Campaign Correpondence - FEIA - Fisher A - E, 1968 (Box 155, Folder 1917-1929)
    - Campaign Correpondence - Fisher F - Z - FOST, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 1930-1941)
    - Campaign Correpondence - FOU - FRENZ, 1968 (Box 157, Folder 1942-1954)
    - Campaign Correpondence - FRER - GARC, 1968 (Box 158, Folder 1955-1966)
    - Campaign Correpondence - GARD - GIK, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 1967-1979)
    - Campaign Correpondence - GIL - GOK, 1968 (Box 160, Folder 1980-1990)
    - Campaign Correpondence - GOL - Green A - I, 1968 (Box 161, Folder 1991-2002)
    - Campaign Correpondence - Green I - Z - GUS, 1968 (Box 162, Folder 2003-2016)
    - Campaign Correpondence - GUT - HALZ, 1968 (Box 163, Folder 2017-2028)
    - Campaign Correpondence - HAM - HARR, 1968 (Box 164, Folder 2029-2038)
    - Campaign Correpondence - HARRIS - HAZ, 1968 (Box 165, Folder 2039-2050)
    - Campaign Correpondence - HEA - HERR, 1968 (Box 166, Folder 2051-2063)
    - Campaign Correpondence - HERS - HOZ, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 2064-2073)
    - Campaign Correpondence - HOD - HORNE, 1968 (Box 168, Folder 2074-2086)
    - Campaign Correpondence - HORNG - HUNT, 1968 (Box 169, Folder 2087-2096)
    - Campaign Correpondence - HUNTA - JACZ, 1968 (Box 170, Folder 2097-2108)
    - Campaign Correpondence - JAE - JOHNSON L - Q, 1968 (Box 171, Folder 2109-2119)
    - Campaign Correpondence - JOHNSON R - Z - JUZ, 1968 (Box 172, Folder 2120-2130)
    - Campaign Correpondence - KA - KELLEY A - I, 1968 (Box 173, Folder 2131-2141)
    - Campaign Correpondence - KELLEY J - Z - KING J - Z, 1968 (Box 174, Folder 2142-2155)
    - Campaign Correpondence - KINGA - KOB, 1968 (Box 175, Folder 2159-2171)
    - Campaign Correpondence - KOD - KUI, 1968 (Box 176, Folder 2172-2182)
    - Campaign Correpondence - KUJ - LARR, 1968 (Box 177, Folder 2183-2193)
    - Campaign Correpondence - LARSE - LEG, 1968 (Box 178, Folder 2194-2206)
    - Campaign Correpondence - LEH - LINC, 1968 (Box 179, Folder 2207-2219)
    - Campaign Correpondence - LINDA - LOU, 1968 (Box 180, Folder 2220-2234)
    - Campaign Correpondence - LOVA - LYZ, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 2235-2243)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MAA - MALL, 1968 (Box 182, Folder 2244-2252)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MALM - MARIZ, 1968 (Box 183, Folder 2253-2261)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MARK - MASZ, 1968 (Box 184, Folder 2262-2270)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MATA - McCK, 1968 (Box 185, Folder 2271-2279)
    - Campaign Correpondence - McCLA - McF, 1968 (Box 186, Folder 2280-2287)
    - Campaign Correpondence - McGA - McMz, 1968 (Box 187, Folder 2288-2294)
    - Campaign Correpondence - McN - MERZ, 1968 (Box 188, Folder 2295-2304)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MESA - MILLER H - J, 1968 (Box 189, Folder 2305-2314)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MILLER I-O - MIZ, 1968 (Box 190, Folder 2315-2322)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MJA - MORF, 1968 (Box 191, Folder 2323-2332)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MORG - MUO, 1968 (Box 192, Folder 2333-2341)
    - Campaign Correpondence - MURA - NEE, 1968 (Box 193, Folder 2342-2349)
    - Campaign Correpondence - NEF - NIE, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 2350-2357)
    - Campaign Correpondence - NIF - OC, 1968 (Box 195, Folder 2358-2365)
    - Campaign Correpondence - ODA - OP, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 2366-2373)